nice to meet you.
初めまして
Isn't it so cute?
めちゃくちゃかわいいじゃないですか?
Maybe I'm used to being told that,
言われ慣れてるかもしれないんですけど、
It looks a lot like a computer.
めっちゃパソコンに似てますね
I get told a lot.
めっちゃ言われます
No, I think that's what it is.
いや、そのものだと思いますよ
Well, actually, it's never happened.
まあ、本当はあったことないんですけど
What is it?
なんですかね
Her style is outstanding, her smile is wonderful,
スタイルも抜群だし、 笑 顔も素敵だし、
That's because I'm fairly new.
結構新人だからですよね
He is approximately 167cm tall.
身長は約167cmです
Wait, you said something a little expensive earlier.
少 し、さっきちょっと高めのこと言ってて、
That seemed expensive, though.
それが高く見えたんですけどね
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
Come here.
このとこ、きて
it's okay.
大丈夫です
thank you.
ありがとうございます
you're welcome.
こちらこそ
Well, little by little.
うーん、少しずつ
Well then, that's right.
じゃあね、そうですね
Now, I would like to ask you a few questions.
では、いくつか質問をさせてもらいますんで
How old was your first match?
あんた、初対戦はいくつぐらいでした?
15 years old.
15歳
13?
High school 1?
高校1?
After entering high school.
高校入ってから
What kind of person was he?
それはあえてはどんな人だったんですか?
We are the same age.
同い年です
Did you say your boyfriend at the time?
当時の彼氏と言った?
that's right.
そうです
After we started dating.
付き合ってから
How was it?
どうでした?
What are your first impressions?
初めての感想は?
But somehow, I was too nervous, not at all.
でもなんか、緊張しすぎて、全然、
I remember...
記憶が...
Maybe I don't remember.
覚えてないかも
On the other hand, do you mean that it didn't hurt that much?
逆に、痛かったとこも、そんなになかったってことですかね?
I was so embarrassed that I couldn't bear it anymore.
もう、それ残るじゃないくらい、恥ずかしかったんですよ
It was strong, like I was nervous.
緊張みたいな、強かった
I don't remember much.
あんまり覚えてないと
By the way, where did you do that?
ちなみに、それは、場所はどこやったんですか?
his house.
彼のお家
In your room.
お部屋で
You made a good house.
ちゃんとお家やったんですね
It's home.
お家ね
I've been listening to this a lot lately, and from my experience at the park,
最近よく聞いてると、 体験から公園で、
I heard that a lot.
とかよく聞いてたんですね
Lately, it's been quite...
最近の頃って、やっぱり結構、まあ...
Go, go.
いけいけ
い け いけ
Well, months have passed since then,
じゃあ、それから、月日は経つんですけど、
In the middle of that, I played a game where I thought, ``Is this a pervert?''
その中で、 ちょっとこれ、私変態だっちゃうかっていうプレイ
Is there anything like that?
とか、 何かありますか?
Well, I wonder what it is.
えー、何だろう
If your tie is untied and you are blindfolded,
ネクタイとかで、 ほどいて、目隠しとかされたら、
I've grown up so much.
めっちゃ、大人になった
Excited.
興奮する
Well, if I were blindfolded.
まあ、私が目隠しだったら
By the way, are you quite a masochist?
ちょっとじゃあ、結構M体質なんですか?
kana?
かな?
Well, if you hear it like that,
まあ、そういう言葉として聞いたら、
I don't have a very masochistic image of gals.
ギャルってなんか、あんまりMっぽいイメージないんですけど
Surprisingly, the M part is also unexpected.
意外と、 Mな部分も、 意外に
That's what it means.
そういうことですね
What else?
他は何ですか?
I wonder what else?
他、何だろう
In the car, and surprisingly, on the go.
車の中とかも、意外と、 行くやつとかも
What do you think?
どうですか?
Well, let's do it with a normal pet,
じゃあ、普通のペットでやるのと、
Do you feel better doing it in a car?
車でやるの、どっちが感じるんですか?
Well, my heart is pounding, so...
え、なんかドキドキするから、 まあ、
There are things that happen.
ありくるのも
Is there no outside?
外がないんですか?
There is outside.
外、あります
At the park.
公園で
At that time, I was a high school girl, so I wore a uniform.
その時は、JKだったから、 制服で、
Like.
みたいな
If you do it in a park, it's on a bench or something.
公園でやると、それは、 ベンチとか、
Or, sideways, standing back, etc.
それとも、 きちんと横で、立ちバックとか、
How do you do it?
どんな感じでやるんですか?
On the bench, was it a bench?
ベンチで、ベンチだったかな?
Do you feel like Zain on the bench?
ベンチで、 ザインみたいな感じですか?
Things like Zain and standing back.
ザインと、立ちバックと、みたいな
JK?
JKか
help me.
助けて
Can you tell me about that park?
その公園、教えてくれる?
I'll go see it.
見に行きますから
Because it's a skirt.
スカートだからね
Did you also go to the park while being a high school girl?
それも、JKながら、 公園してたんですか?
I was doing it.
してました
It's tough, isn't it?
大変ですね
There may have been something like that in Kawasaki.
川崎の、そういうのがあったかもしれないんですけど、
Isn't there something wrong?
なんか、 なんか ないですか?
Eh, I wonder what it is.
えー、なんだろう
Perverted chick thing?
変態チックなこと?
Well, something like Abknowman.
まあ、アブノウマンとか
I don't know.
わからん
I wonder what it is.
なんだろうな
How about multiple?
複数とかどうですか?
Sure, I might be interested, but I've never done it.
確かに、興味はあるかも、 やったことない
In that case, the position of the mince is to hand it over to the man, or
その場合は、メンチとしては、 男性に渡す位置か、
Or what it feels like to listen to a female friend.
それとも、女友達との 耳とか、どんな感じが、
I'm masking it inside myself.
自分の中でマスキングしてる
2nd place for men is good.
男性2位がいいですね
I want to be attacked by Japan.
日本に、日本で攻められたい
I want to be attacked.
攻められたい
What happened in Japan?
日本でどんなことされたんですか?
Eh, I wonder what it is.
えー、なんだろう
I want to be attacked.
襲われたい
There were two men, so I was able to enter normally,
男性2人なんで、 普通に正常に入れられながら、
While being put in from behind, being lent anus,
バックで入れられながら、 アナルムを貸されるとか、
What do you think?
どうですか?
Yes.
ありです
What is experiential?
何が経験的なんですか?
It's done.
済みです
It's a change.
変化ですね
Is that so?
なのかな?
What do you like most about playing?
何が一番、プレイとしては好きですか?
difficult.
難しい
What do you like most?
何が一番好き?
I get most excited when something is happening to me.
何されてるときは、一番興奮します
If you're being misplaced.
ズラされてたりすると
Stipossoli.
スティポッソリ
How many cups of brain bone is there?
脳骨は何カップぐらいですか?
It's C.
Cです
That's nice.
いいですね
What do you think?
どうですか?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
The waist is thin.
ウェストが細い
I don't know.
知らん
It's a waste, isn't it?
無駄ですね
Are you serious?
本気か
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
None.
無い
Are you an insider?
内派ですか?
Is Mao an insider?
毛は内派ですか?
It's an inner faction.
内派です
Can I have it opened for you?
開けてもらっていいですか?
No hair at all.
毛が全然ない
What do you think?
どうですか?
My uncle is sleeping a lot.
おじさんがいっぱい寝てますけど
Excited.
興奮する
How are you feeling?
どんな気分ですか?
Horny.
ムラムラ
Looks big.
デカそう
How do you feel about Deca?
デカの気持ちはどうですか?
like.
好き
It came out.
出てきました
出てきた
delicious?
美味しい?
It came out.
出てきました
It's the best to flick the ball around on your own.
勝手に球をサワサワするの最高
That's right.
当たってますね
Is that how you always do it?
いつもそうやってしてあげるんですか?
Sawa-chan.
サワちゃん
Yes, I do it every month.
うん、毎月してます
What do you think?
どうかな?
It feels so good.
すごい気持ちいいな
ERROR
ズボン引っ張ってもらっていいですか?
言わせます
It's often said.
よく言われますよ
Can you tell me?
言ってくれるかな?
guess.
当てる
Sperm is coming out every day from my tummy.
たまんぼかに精子が毎日これ出てる
May I?
いいですか?
It's out.
出てるね
What is it?
なんだろう?
Try stopping the sperm.
精子をストップしてみて
Like Stell?
ステルみたいに?
amazing.
すごい
My mouth is so full
すっごい口までいっぱ
I'll put it in.
い 入れちゃう
oh
お
belly full
腹 いっぱ
stomach.
い
drink?
飲 む?
I drank it.
飲んだ
I slept with a full stomach.
お腹いっぱい寝てた
In terms of density.
濃さ的に
It was delicious.
美味しかったです
Rich.
濃厚
100 points.
100点
Shall I show you my body for the next punishment game?
次回の罰ゲームの体を見せていただこうか
That's one piece.
それワンピースですね
One Piece.
ワンピースね
1 piece.
1枚
Can I have it removed?
抜いてもらっていいですか?
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
wonderful.
素晴らしい
I'm full.
お 腹いっぱい
Great breathing.
素晴らしい呼吸が
Only this one.
こっちだけ
Can I have your legs removed?
足を抜いてもらっていいですか?
Please be careful.
気をつけてください
From below.
下から
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Can I open it normally?
普段は開けてもいいですか?
Can I open it?
開けてもいいですか?
開 けて もいいですか?
Can I open it?
開けてもいいですか?
few
少
When you come over here, press your left foot here.
し こっちに来たら、 左足をここに押して
left foot.
左足
Right foot.
右足
Sawa Sawa.
サワサワ
Kinkin.
キンキン
feet
足
Can I have it removed too?
も 抜いてもらっていいですか?
yes.
はい
Can I have you add some bubbles?
少し泡をつけてもらっていいですか?
How to wash the bottom.
下の洗い方が
Create a backstory.
裏筋を作る
You can get the ball to bounce as it is.
そのまま、球もサワサワしてもらえる
Please be careful.
気をつけてください
Let me help you
手 を つ かってもらって
May I?
いい ですか?
Can I ask you to be careful three times?
3回、気をつけてもらっていいですか?
Please get started quickly.
早く、手をつけてください
Please be careful.
気 を つけてください
My hair was scratched too much.
髪が掻かれすぎた
It's a nice bath.
いいお風呂です
I got a lot of it on my face though.
顔にいっぱい掛かっちゃいましたけど
You can put sweets and warm spirits on your face.
お菓子とか、温かい精神を顔に掛けられるの
happy.
嬉しい
Can I have Fushido hold me in that state?
その状態で、 フシドに持たれてもらっていいですか?
Can you push me a little more?
もう少し押してもらっていいですか?
No hair at all.
毛が全くない
sometimes?
たまに?
what?
何?
What is it?
何だろう?
Toys?
おもちゃ?
What would you use it for?
何で使うかな?
Use with vibrator.
バイブで使う
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Can I try one more?
もう一個試していいですか?
Anal plus.
アナルプラスです
I saw it for the first time.
初めて見た
Which do you want to do?
どっちをどうしたいですか?
Want to get stronger?
もっと強くしたいですか?
It's ticklish just now, isn't it?
いったばっかりでくすぐったいんでしょ?
It's a little pushy.
少し押し気になります
Do men feel the best?
男が一番気持ちいいですか?
What do you think?
どうですか?
A little more.
もう少し
It's been a while since I've had anal plus.
久しぶりのアナルプラスです
Feels good.
気持ちいい
Which do you think is better?
思うことはどっちがいいですか?
Which one is better?
どっちがいい?
How do you feel about this feeling?
このお気持ちの入れ心地はどうですか?
After 2 shots, I feel better again.
2発出したらまた元気が
Can I have you look at this name while doing this?
こっちのネームズを見ながらしてもらっていいですか?
I felt like everyone should take a look.
みんな見てくれという感じで
Do you want a girl?
女 の 子 さん欲しいですか?
towards the front.
前に向かって
Please improve that condition.
その状態を上げてもらって
Here too.
ここも
So do it like this.
それでこうやって
Please move your feet a little closer
もう少し足を寄せてもらって
May I?
いい ですか?
What do you think?
どうですか?
Feels good.
気 持 ちいい
my?
私の?